http://www.inclusive.co.uk/privacy-policy

We are always open online and delivering safely.
Need support? We are available and ready to help by phone, email, or LiveChat.
Products
Content & Articles
Your Shopping Basket:
Register
Change Currency:
£ UK | $ US | € EUR
HomeShopVirtual DemosNewsArticlesTechnical SupportVideosJobsContact Us
You are in: Home > Privacy Policy
What's New?iPad AppsClearance SaleSoftware
Communication SoftwareCurriculum SoftwareDyslexia SoftwareEarly Learning SoftwareEye Gaze SoftwareInclusive Technology SoftwareiPad AppsKeyboard/Typing Skills SoftwareOlder Learners SoftwareSoftware BundlesSwitch Accessible SoftwareVisual Impairment Software
Hardware
Alternative KeyboardsAlternative MiceCollars & Arm SupportsCommunication DevicesEducational TechnologyEnvironmental ControlEye Gaze TechnologyInclusive KitsiPad Access, Accessories & CasesMounting SolutionsSensory Technology & PlaySimply Works RangeSpeech & Hearing AmplifiersSwitch Adapted ToysSwitchesSwitch InterfacesTouch Screen TechnologyTrolleys, Tables & StorageVirtual Reality
Favourite Products
HelpKidzLearn Games and Activities
From: £72.00
ChooseIt! Maker 3
From: £72.00
ChooseIt! Readymades
From: £72.00
n-ABLER Joystick
Fax: 01457 819799
Email:
inclusive@inclusive.co.uk
Sign up NOW!for our email newsletter
Privacy Policy
INTRODUCTION:
This website is owned and operated by Inclusive Technology Ltd ("Inclusive Technology", "we", "us", "our"), whose registered address is at Riverside Court, Huddersfield Road, Delph, Oldham, OL3 5FZ. Inclusive Technology is a global provider for educational institutions of fun, accessible games, activities, and tools designed specifically for young children and those with learning difficulties ("Services").
This privacy policy ("Policy") sets out how Inclusive Technology processes personal information collected through our websites (including www.helpkidzlearn.com and www.inclusive.co.uk) (each a ""Website"). It is important that you read this Policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This Policy supplements any additional notices and is not intended to override them.
Inclusive Technology is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Accordingly, we adhere to the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) ("GDPR") and any applicable industry and regulatory guidelines. We regularly review and update our Policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of personal information in our possession.
You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office ("ICO"), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.
Personal Information we collect
You may access certain areas of the Website without providing any personal information at all. However, to use all features and functions available on the Website you may be required to submit certain personal information.
Without limitation, Inclusive Technology may collect any of the following personal information (which is information that identifies you or relates to you as an identifiable person) from time to time:
Information you provide us
We collect personal information on the Website when Users choose to reveal it to us. For example, when you register an account with us, when you sign up to attend an event, when you contact us to request a demonstration of our products or services, when you otherwise send us questions, we will collect personal information such as name, email address, telephone and fax numbers, username, password, job title and role, professional contact details, postal address and postcode, preferences and interests, financial information such as credit / debit card numbers, feedback on our products or services.
Where you choose to provide it, we may collect sensitive personal information on the Website, such as dietary requirements, sensory and diagnosis information, (or other health related data).
You may also provide us with your personal information on the publicly accessible blogs on our Website. You should be aware that any personal information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at info@helpkidzlearn.com or inclusive@inclusive.co.uk. In some cases we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Personal Information collected automatically
We may collect common information found in communications sent over the Internet, from which we can often infer such things as: (1) browser type (e.g., Chrome or Internet Explorer); (2) operating system (e.g., Mac OS or Windows); (3) browser language (e.g., English or Spanish); (4) Internet Protocol (IP) address; (5) Internet Service Provider (e.g., BT); (6) geolocation and (7) a list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on this Website, and the site you exit to (automatically collected). This information may be personal information.
Personal information used to contact you and for Marketing
When you sign up for our Services on our Website, we will use your name and email address to send newsletters and other useful information to you regarding our Services. You may at any time choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the emails you receive or by contacting us via email at info@helpkidzlearn.com or inclusive@inclusive.co.uk.
Information we receive from third parties
We may receive personal information about you from a third party such as your employer, social media platforms, public databases and lead generation service providers. This may include your name, contact details and interests and preferences.
Use of personal information
We will only use personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data if:
we need to so we can perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you;
it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests; or
we need to so we can comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing personal data other than in relation to sending direct marketing communications to you via email or text message. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us at info@helpkidzlearn.com or inclusive@inclusive.co.uk.
However if you provide us with sensitive personal data you consent to us processing it for the performance of a contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you, to identify types of customers for our products and services, and to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy.
The information we collect through our Website helps us to provide you with the best possible services and experience when using our Website, to identify ways that we can continue to serve our customers in the best way possible and for the reasons set out in the table below. We have also identified the legal basis on which we rely to process your personal data as well as our legitimate interest, where appropriate.
Purpose/Activity
Type of data
Lawful basis for processing
To process payment, delivery services and other contract fulfilment requirements including to contact you with sales related information or assistance. We will request your prior consent where required by applicable law
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Financial
(d) Transaction
(e) Marketing and Communications
(a) Performance of a contract with you
(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)
To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services or an event in which you are attending and changes to our terms, of use and policies
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Profile
(d) Marketing and Communications
(a) Performance of a contract with you
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)
For internal record keeping
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Financial
(d) Transaction
(e) Marketing and Communications
(a) Performance of a contract with you
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated)
To improve our Website, products and services, such as by data analytics
(a) Technical
(b) Usage
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)
For transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Profile
(d) Marketing and Communications
(a) Performance of a contract with you
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)
To contact you for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail (such information may be used to customise or update the Website)
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)
To determine how you found out about us and what your interests are regarding our Services
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Usage
(d) Profile
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)
To help recognise a unique computer or device so that we can deliver relevant ads to you, measure the impact of the ads and better understand and recognise digital media usage patterns (the technologies described in the cookies section below)
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Technical
(d) Usage
(e) Profile
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)
For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Technical
(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise, to develop our products/services and grow our business)
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
As we believe to be necessary or appropriate under applicable law, to comply with legal process, to respond to requests from public and government authorities, to protect and pursue our rights
(a) Identity
(b) Contact
(c) Technical
(d) Usage
(e) Profile
(a) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
Sharing and disclosing your personal information
Other than as expressly set out in this Policy or as otherwise required or permitted by law, we will not share, sell, or distribute any of your personal information without your consent.
Inclusive Technology may, from time to time, employ the services of other persons for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment processing, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, data hosting, advertising, marketing, and sales. We take measures to require such third parties to protect the confidentiality of your personal information in accordance with the standards described in this Policy.
In addition, where you have contacted us on behalf of your employer, we may share certain personal information with your employer, where required in order to provide the Services requested.
Because aggregated or anonymised information does not personally identify you, we may use it for any purpose. If we combine anonymised or aggregated data with personal information, we will treat the combined information as personal information according to this Policy.
Marketing
We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased goods and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.
You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by contacting us at any time at info@helpkidzlearn.com or inclusive@inclusive.co.uk.
We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside the Inclusive Technology group of companies for marketing purposes.
International transfers
We provide our Services globally and as such, subject to applicable law, may transfer your information to selected third parties outside the country where you are located and where information protection standards may differ. We will take steps to ensure that your personal information is only transferred once adequate safeguards are in place.
Links to Other Websites
This Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. Inclusive Technology has no control over third party websites you may go to from our Website and is in no way responsible for the content thereof. This Policy does not extend to your use of those websites. Users are encouraged to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them.
Changes of Business Ownership and Control
Inclusive Technology may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of Inclusive Technology. Personal information provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the personal information for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.
In the event that any personal information submitted by Users is to be transferred in such a manner, as required under applicable law, you will be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.
Your Rights in relation to your Personal Information
You are entitled to know what personal information we hold about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes/corrections to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date.
You can access the personal information that we hold on you by logging into your account and making any changes to your personal information as necessary. You are also entitled to request that we give you access to, correct or delete any personal information that we hold about you, subject to any lawful exemptions. You can also ask us to transfer the personal data we hold about you to another person, or delete your account altogether.
If you have registered an account with us, it is your responsibility to ensure that you submit true, accurate, and complete information to your account, and keep it up to date. You may also update your personal information by contacting us through the contact details provided below. We may from time to time reach out to you to ensure the personal information you provide is up to date in any case.
If you have any questions about the personal information that we hold about you, would like us to correct or delete such data, or would like to request access to it so you may view it yourself, please contact us using the contact information provided. Where you have requested that we provide your personal information to you, you will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive, or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances. We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.
Security
Data security is of great importance to Inclusive Technology and to protect your personal information we have put in place adequate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure personal information collected via this Website.
Cookies
This Website may place and access certain Cookies on your computer. Inclusive Technology uses Cookies to improve your experience of using the Website and to improve our range of products and services. Inclusive Technology has carefully chosen these Cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and respected at all times.
The types of technologies used via the Website include:
Cookies: Small text files that contain a string of characters.Inclusive Technology uses cookies to uniquely identify an Internet browser. Certain browsers or browser settings sometimes block cookies, and cookies may not work effectively on some mobile devices. For more information about cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org
Pixel Tags: Transparent images, iFrames, or JavaScript that our clients and partners use to understand how consumers interact with them online, including on websites and in mobile apps. They are also commonly known as web beacons.
Statistical IDs: Created via an algorithm using non-personally identifiable and pseudonymous information about your computer or device, including your operating system, user-agent string, IP address (in certain jurisdictions), Internet browser, installed fonts, and similar information. This information makes your computer or device distinct enough for our systems to determine within a reasonable probability that they are encountering the same computer or device, including in environments where cookies are not supported.
The types of technologies used via the Website include cookies. Some cookies that we use are necessary for the service to function properly. In addition we may also use "functional" cookies that allow the service to remember choices you have made so as to provide a more personalised and enhanced user experience.
If you do not wish us to install cookies on your device for these purposes, you may change the settings on your browser to reject cookies. Please note that if you do set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of the Website and/or service. This Website places the following cookies:
Name of cookie
Purpose
Strictly necessary?
.ASPAUTH
Allows the user to remain logged in for a fixed period
No
ASP.NET_SessionId
Contains an id that identifies the users' session
Yes
The Website uses analytics services provided by Google Analytics. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse usage statistics, enabling us to better understand how Users use the Website. This, in turn, enables us to improve the Website and the products and services offered through it. You do not have to allow us to use these Cookies, as detailed below. However, whilst our use of analytics Cookies does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of the Website it does enable us to continually improve our business and ultimately the Services you use.
The analytics service used by the Website uses cookies to gather the required information. Certain of these cookies may be placed immediately when you decide to visit the Website and it may not be possible to obtain your prior consent. To remove these cookies and prevent future use of them, refer to your internet browser’s help documentation for instructions.
The analytics service uses the following cookies:
Name
1st/3rd party
Provider
Purpose
_utma
Third
Google
This cookie is typically written to the browser upon the first visit from that web browser. If the cookie has been deleted by the browser operator, and the browser subsequently visits your site, a new __utma cookie is written with a different unique ID. This cookie is used to determine unique visitors to the site and it is updated with each page view. Additionally, this cookie is provided with a unique ID that Google Analytics uses to ensure both the validity and accessibility of the cookie as an extra security measure.
_utmb
Third
Google
This cookie is used to establish and continue a user session. When a user views a page on the site, the Google Analytics code attempts to update this cookie. If it does not find the cookie, a new one is written and a new session is established. Each time a user visits a different page on the site, this cookie is updated to expire in 30 minutes, thus continuing a single session for as long as user activity continues within 30-minute intervals. This cookie expires when a user pauses on a page on the site for longer than 30 minutes.
_utmz
Third
Google
This cookie stores the type of referral used by the visitor to reach the site, whether via a direct method, a referring link, a website search, or a campaign such as an ad or an email link. It is used to calculate search engine traffic, ad campaigns and page navigation within your own site. The cookie is updated with each page view to the site.
_cco
Third
Captchaco
The site uses Captchaco tracking to understand who has visited the website, which pages they have viewed and the number of times they have visited. This cookie is used to identify each visitor each time that they return to the site.
Managing Cookies
You can choose to enable or disable cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all cookies or only third party cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser.
You can choose to delete cookies at any time however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Website more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, personalisation settings.
It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.
Data Retention
If you send us information or create an account on our Website, we will retain your information for as long as your account is active with us or for as long as you are receiving our Services. Please be advised that even after you have closed your account with us or ceased to use our Services, we may retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Cookies set via the Website will expire within two years.
Information provided on someone else’s behalf
If you provide us with information about someone else, please ensure you have the person’s permission to do so for the purposes detailed in this Policy.
By providing personal data relating to another person, you confirm that you have their consent to do so, or are entitled to consent to the processing on their behalf (for example for children where you have parental responsibility).
Our customers
To the extent you are a customer of Inclusive Technology, you acknowledge that you have your own obligations in relation to the personal information you provide to us and that we process on your behalf. It is your responsibility to ensure that any information shared with us is done so in accordance with the laws applicable to you.
Changes to this Policy
From time to time we may revise this Policy. If we make revisions that change or affect whether or how we collect or use personal information we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our Website thirty days prior to the change becoming effective. In any event, you should review the Website periodically so that you are up-to-date on our most current policies and practices.
Contact
If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy then please contact us at info@helpkidzlearn.com or inclusive@inclusive.co.uk or by sending correspondence to:
Inclusive Technology Limited, Riverside Court, Huddersfield Road, Delph, Oldham OL3 5FZ, UK
Home
|
Shop
|
Virtual Demos
|
News
|
Copyright © Inclusive Technology Ltd 2001 2020
Inclusive Technology Registered Office: Riverside Court, Huddersfield Road, Delph . Oldham. OL3 5FZ
Registered in England, Company registration number: 3525459. VAT no: GB732822345
Website design & development:
X
Data is at the heart of everything we do. It’s what allows us to create bespoke, accessible online services for your learners. For that reason, we take protecting your data very seriously.
Updated Terms and Privacy Policy
Inclusive Technology will always hold and use your data securely, responsibly and transparently. With new European data protection laws (GDPR), we have taken the opportunity to update our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.
Cookies
This website uses cookies to improve your overall experience. More information about them can be found in our Privacy Policy. If you wish, you can change your cookie settings in your browser.
Thank you for your continued support.
